[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "Eva, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "I'm good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "Lovely to have you in my studio.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "What do you mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Occupation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "What do you call yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Actor is on there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "That excites me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Yes, one of those things that I mentioned.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "I mean like when you're older you have a better appreciation for history or for knowledge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "What are you -- what are you actually studying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Chicano studies and political science.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "What is Chicano studies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Chicano studies is the study mostly of the Mexican- American movement that has happened in the United States, and the history of Mexican-Americans.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Can I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "You can be an honorary Chicano?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "You can be an honorary Chicano.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "What do I have to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Well, you have to help us in the fight for social justice and believe in equality for everyone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "How important are your roots to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Pretty important.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "You had to learn Spanish?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Do you speak French?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "I speak a bit of French.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Immigration?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "When I came here, I couldn't believe the hot issue it really is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "How would you fix things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well, that's a loaded question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Do you think he has lived up to expectations?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "I think he had a lot on his plate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "It's heartbreaking to see kids having to do this in modern ages, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "The great thing about this documentary is that -- actually we produced it so it can be used as a political tool to change the way agricultural workers are treated in the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "You're quite an activist, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "You shouldn't be, but I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "How do you deal with that as someone who's got in your own family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "How is she doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "She's doing amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "I mean, to have somebody in your life who, none of that means anything to at all and who's not impressed by any of that because why would she be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "It makes it very natural for you, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "She's very grounding.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "Don't you find that a bit unsettling when you go home?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "No entourage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "What's the matter with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "I'm really not a complainer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Do we say slouch, lay back, think of England?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", ",", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "I'm going to go sit in your lap.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Why do you think I put you in an uncomfortable chair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Yes, I tweet a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Demi Moore", "Ashton"]}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "What's the attraction of Twitter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "You know it's funny because Demi Moore and Ashton were, like, you know, the really pioneers of getting everybody on Twitter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Are you a drunk tweeter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "No, not drunk tweeting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "It's more to do with putting stuff out there where you -- why did I do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "EX", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Like if you choose to make your life so public?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Because it's so easy now to become a celebrity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "No, because I mean -- really I don't really care.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "You're look like a mini Oprah, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oprah"]}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "What's the Eva Longoria brand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Well, I think similar to Oprah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Eva Longoria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Are you tough enough to be a mogul, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Are you not to be messed with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "I am not to be messed with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "I mean seriously, could you ever go out with a man with a soft handshake?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Who?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I'm not going to name them now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Who taught you direct eye contact and firm handshake?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Probably my family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "They're all strong women, aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "And they're all strong, strong women.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "What do they make -- what do they make of what's happened to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "They're proud.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Are they -- do they quite believe it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Well, I was always different.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Do I like being famous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Or does it make no difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Did you imagine you would be married for life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "But did you really believe this was the guy, this was the one for you for life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "It all came out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "The marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Do you feel humiliated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "A bit, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "What more could a guy want, frankly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJR", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Well, you know, like I said, we just -- you want different things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Is there any way back as far as you're concerned, if a man behaves that way towards you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Do you think he wants to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Would you get married again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Oh, that's a horrible question to ask when I just got divorced.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "It's not top of your list, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Are you actually divorced yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Yes, we've been divorced for a while.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "How old is your wife?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "She's 10 years younger than me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "I recommend it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", ":"], "qSentId": 647, "question": "I mean, even though she's younger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Tell me about your --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "Do you mind when those pictures come out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "Do you like being in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "I love being in love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "Once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "And you married him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "And I married him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "How many times have you been in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "More than that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "NN", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "What's the next subject?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "Well, you did say move on, but I think we'll stick around for a while if you don't mind.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", ":", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Has what happened to you damaged your ability to love, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "You know, I thought it would -- was actually really, was really disappointed in the concept of loyalty and faithfulness and things like that, but, no, I can't let it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "What is the way to have a civilized break?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "Did that particularly worry you, that you kind of reached a point in a relationship where you were about to have children and suddenly it's not the future you thought you had?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "It's still my future, I still will have children.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 745, "question": "I mean, are you in an exclusive situation with your playboy or is there a door opening here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 746, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 758, "question": "If you had a dream number, what it would be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 759, "answer": "It would be four.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "Oh, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 812, "question": "Why should I get excited by your cookbook?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 813, "answer": "I love to cook.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 824, "question": "Oh, it's called guac, is it, you call in the trade?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 825, "answer": "Well, guacamole.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 832, "question": "Now, are these your little signature things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBP", "DT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 833, "answer": "These are my signature things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 852, "question": "Now the interview starts, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 853, "answer": "I love margaritas.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 856, "question": "But this is all quite simple food, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 857, "answer": "It's all very simple and, you know, I'm not a chef.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 865, "question": "Do you think there's someone watching this who can't cook, like me, if they read this book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 866, "answer": "If you can read, you can cook.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 894, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 895, "answer": "You know, the people you reach.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 901, "question": "Oh, God, what are you going to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 902, "answer": "Sex.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 914, "question": "Did she tell you that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 915, "answer": "She told me that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 916, "question": "On air?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 917, "answer": "No, it wasn't on air, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 923, "question": "None?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 924, "answer": "Good for Gwyn.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 930, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 931, "answer": "I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 938, "question": "When you see the Oscars on TV, do you think -- do you start practicing the speech that may never happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 939, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 945, "question": "Do you like politics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 946, "answer": "I actually love --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 961, "question": "Can you imagine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 962, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 965, "question": "What about Oprah-Eva ticket?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 966, "answer": "ONGORIA: I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 971, "question": "What's been the moment you'd relive tomorrow if you had the chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 972, "answer": "You know, people ask me this all the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andy Garcia"]}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ":", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 990, "question": "Any movies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 991, "answer": "Well, yes, I just did -- finished a film called \"Cristiada\" with Andy Garcia.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["fall"]}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 996, "question": "When's it out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 997, "answer": "In the fall.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]